{
    "subject": "Daniel_Rodney",
    "predicate": "livesIn",
    "object": "Lewes _Delaware",
    "human_readable": "Daniel Rodney lives in Lewes, Delaware.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9692621231079102,
            "question": "Could Daniel Rodney be found in Lewes, Delaware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8641955852508545,
            "question": "Is Daniel Rodney from Lewes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8302990794181824,
            "question": "Where does Daniel Rodney live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7507187128067017,
            "question": "What is the name of the place Daniel Rodney lives in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.746055006980896,
            "question": "In which location does Daniel Rodney reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7252453565597534,
            "question": "Name the city where Daniel Rodney resides."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5573011040687561,
            "question": "Does Daniel Rodney call Lewes home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4763600528240204,
            "question": "What state is Lewes in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3202134668827057,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Daniel Rodney, where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2903939485549927,
            "question": "Is Lewes a city?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Daniel Rodney lives in Lewes, Delaware.",
            "html": "yago_8268_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to visit Daniel Rodney, where would you go?",
            "html": "yago_8268_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Lewes in?",
            "html": "yago_8268_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Daniel Rodney call Lewes home?",
            "html": "yago_8268_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8268_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple in question is:\n\n\"Daniel Rodney lives in Lewes, Delaware.\"\n\nGiven the context information and without prior knowledge, we can evaluate this triple as follows:\n\n* The documents mention that Daniel Rodney was born at Lewes in the Delaware Colony (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8268/re-ranker-msmarco/100.txt).\n* The documents also mention that Daniel Rodney's family lived at 231 Second Street and were members of St. Peter's Episcopal Church in Lewes (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8268/re-ranker-msmarco/100.txt).\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that Daniel Rodney lives in Lewes, Delaware.\n\nThe final answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Daniel Rodney lives in Lewes, Delaware.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate that Daniel Rodney was born in and had ties to Lewes, Sussex County, Delaware, including his birthplace, family connections, and business activities."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}